[
  {
    "question_text": "What's the capital of Bulgaria?",
    "right_answer": "Sofia",
    "wrong_answers": ["Budapest", "Bucharest", "Lyubljana"]
  },
  {
    "question_text": "What's the capital of Slovenia?",
    "right_answer": "Lyubljana",
    "wrong_answers": ["Budapest", "Bucharest", "Sofia"]
  },
  {
    "question_text": "What's the capital of Spain?",
    "right_answer": "Madrid",
    "wrong_answers": ["Paris", "Portu", "Barcelona"]
  },
  {
    "question_text": "What's the capital of Poland?",
    "right_answer": "Warsaw",
    "wrong_answers": ["Krakov", "Lviv", "Kiev"]
  },
  {
    "question_text": "What's the capital of Norway?",
    "right_answer": "Oslo",
    "wrong_answers": ["Prague", "Helsinki", "Talin"]
  },
  {
    "question_text": "What's the capital of Portugal?",
    "right_answer": "Lisbon",
    "wrong_answers": ["Portu", "Madrid", "Paris"]
  },
  {
    "question_text": "What's the capital of Finland?",
    "right_answer": "Helsinkhy",
    "wrong_answers": ["Budapest", "Talin", "Oslo"]
  },
  {
    "question_text": "What's the capital of Belarus?",
    "right_answer": "Minsk",
    "wrong_answers": ["Zagreb", "Kharkiv", "Moscow"]
  },
  {
    "question_text": "What's the capital of Russia?",
    "right_answer": "Moscow",
    "wrong_answers": ["St. Petersburg", "Kiev", "Minsk"]
  },
  {
    "question_text": "What's the capital of Croatia?",
    "right_answer": "Zagreb",
    "wrong_answers": ["Warsaw", "Helsinki", "Talin"]
  }
]
